{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Theatre",
                "Funfair",
                "Aquarium",
                "Campsite"
            ],
            "question": "Where can you go to watch the fish swim?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Campsite",
                "Aquarium",
                "Theatre",
                "Funfair"
            ],
            "question": "Where do people dance around the campfire?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Ride horses",
                "Listen to music",
                "Jog",
                "Play chess"
            ],
            "question": "If you want to relax and enjoy sounds, you should ...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "d",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Watch the fish",
                "Jog",
                "Dance around the campfire",
                "Ride horses"
            ],
            "question": "Which activity involves sitting on an animal and moving around?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Funfair",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "People go to a ... to enjoy exciting rides and games.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Theatre",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "If you want to watch a live play, you should visit a ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Jog",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "To stay fit, many people wake up early to ... in the park.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Play chess",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "A strategic game that requires thinking skills is called ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Watch the fish",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "At the aquarium, visitors can ... swimming in the tanks.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Wonderful",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "Going to the funfair and riding the roller coasters is a ... experience!",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}